/* jshint esversion: 11 */
const question = [{
    question: "Which player scored the most tries in the 2014 tournament?",
    option1: "Andrew Trimble",
    option2: "Johnny Sexton",
    option3: "Rob Kearney",
    answer: "2",
},
    {   
    question: "Where did Ireland finish on the table in 2005?",
    option1: "2nd",
    option2: "3rd",
    option3: "4th",
    option4: "1st",
    answer: "2",
    },

    {
    question: "What was the final score of Ireland's Grand Slam winning match against Wales in 2009?",
    option1: "14-16",
    option2: "16-18",
    option3: "15-17",
    option4: "19-21",
    answer: "3",
    },

    {
    question: "Who did Ireland play in their very first Six Nations game back in 2000?",
    option1: "Scotland",
    option2: "Wales",
    option3: "France",
    option4: "England",
    answer: "4",
    },

    {
    question: "Who were Ireland playing in the 2007 final round before France denied them a championship on points difference?",
    option1: "Italy",
    option2: "Scotland",
    option3: "Wales",
    option4: "France",
    answer: "1",
    },

    {
    question: "Who scored Ireland's only try when they beat England in Twickenham in 2004?",
    option1: "Brian O'Driscoll",
    option2: "Girvan Dempsey",
    option3: "Shane Horgan",
    answer: "2",
    },

    {
    question: "How many games did Ireland win in the 2008 tournament?",
    option1: "Two",
    option2: "Three",
    option3: "Four",
    option4: "One",
    answer: "1"
    },

    {
    question: "Who ended up playing on the wing against Italy in 2013?",
    option1: "Sean Cronin",
    option2: "Peter O'Mahony",
    option3: "Sean O'Brien",
    option4: "Paul O'Connell",
    answer: "2",
    },

    {
    question: "Who won Player of The Championship in 2010?",
    option1: "Tommy Bowe",
    option2: "Paul O'Connell",
    option3: "Brian O'Driscoll",
    option4: "Johnny Sexton",
    answer: "1",
    },

    {
    question: "In what was Ireland's game against France postponed due to frost?",
    option1: "2010",
    option2: "2011",
    option3: "2012",
    option4: "2009",
    answer: "3",
    },
];

